# BESIAN BERISHA

WEB DEVELOPER - IT SUPPORT NETWORK MANAGEMENT



besikeksi@gmail.com

Q Gjakova, Kosovo 50000

# SKILLS

- · Web Design
- IT Support
- Troubleshooting--
- · technical issues
- · Solving problems (also
- network)
- Database SQL
   Strong Communication

## **EDUCATION**

#### **BACHELOR OF COMPUTER SCIENCE**

University of Prizren Computer Science: Software Design 2016-2019

### MASTER OF COMPUTER SCIENCE

University of Prizren

Computer Science and Communication

Technology

2020- 2023

## **PROFILE**

I am a qualified and professional IT technical problems solving with over 10 years of experience in Troubleshooting , Windows System administration and network problems solving. Strong creative and analytical skills, details in problems also front end developer.

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### APPLICATIONS DEVELOPER

KRU Radoniqi Dukagjini Sh.A

2021 - Present

- Database administration and website design
- IT Support
- Network Management
   Windows system administration

#### **WEB CONTENT**

2016-2018

- Front End
- · Web Problems Solving

# TRAINING CERTIFICATES

ADMINISTRATIVE ASSISTANT (2016-2017)

MANAGER OF MICRO AND SMALL ENTERPRISES(2019) SQL

Server Querying Data with Transact-SQL (American University of Kosovo - AUK) (2022)